<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Adriana Saldana &#8211; Audible Magic</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.audiblemagic.com/author/adriana-saldana/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.audiblemagic.com</link>
	<description>Automatic Content Recognition (ACR) &#38; Rights Management Solutions</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.audiblemagic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Adriana Saldana &#8211; Audible Magic</title>
	<link>https://www.audiblemagic.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Audible Magic and Stadeum Sports Partner to Fight Piracy in Romania</title>
		<link>https://www.audiblemagic.com/2019/07/22/audible-magic-and-stadeum-sports-partner-to-fight-piracy-in-romania/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Adriana Saldana]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 20:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ACR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Content Recognition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Content Identification]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content recognition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[music identification service]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social media networks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social networks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sports leagues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video ID]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://audiblemagic.flywheelstaging.com/?p=5109</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Using Audible Magic’s technology, Stadeum works on social media platforms to remove infringing pages that often host unauthorized live or pre-recorded video content.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.audiblemagic.com/2019/07/22/audible-magic-and-stadeum-sports-partner-to-fight-piracy-in-romania/">Audible Magic and Stadeum Sports Partner to Fight Piracy in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.audiblemagic.com">Audible Magic</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Partnership Protects Liga Profesionista de Fotbal Club Content Across Social Media Networks</strong></p>
<p>July 23, 2019 (LOS GATOS, Calif.) – Audible Magic, the industry standard for content identification linked to digital rights, and <a href="https://www.stadeumsports.com/">Stadeum Sports</a>, who is digitally transforming football in Romania, announced a partnership to fight piracy impacting sports leagues in Romania. Using Audible Magic’s technology, Stadeum works on social media platforms to remove infringing pages that often host unauthorized live or pre-recorded video content.</p>
<p>Stadeum monitors social media networks on behalf of Romania’s professional football league <a href="https://www.lpf.ro/">Liga Profesionista de Fotbal</a> (LPF) and its 14 member clubs. The company works diligently with social media platforms to take down fake pages, and unauthorized video clips and live streams of matches. Additionally, through their partnership with Audible Magic, Stadeum protects against unauthorized sharing and enables authorized club content to be legitimately shared on their official social media networks.</p>
<p>“I am very thankful to Audible Magic and Stadeum Sports for their engagement and support in this important LPF initiative,” said Robert Pongracz vice president of LPF. “We consider the fight against piracy an essential objective to increase the value of our IP in the future. This step will provide us great opportunities to further develop the game in the digital world and to deliver huge benefits for the football community and our member clubs.”</p>
<p>Audible Magic’s Emmy Award<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> winning technology fingerprints registered content that has been provided to Stadeum by the football clubs. Once the authorized content has been registered it is assigned a unique fingerprint, which can be identified across the social platforms that Audible Magic has relationships with. This process ensures the legitimate use of audio and video content, including live streams of media in real-time, for the rightful owner.</p>
<p>“As the pioneer of automated content recognition, we view our foray into sporting events as a natural extension for the use of our technology,” said Vance Ikezoye, president and chief executive officer at Audible Magic. “The process of registering content to prevent unauthorized use of audio and video, both pre-recorded and live events, will allow the LPF football clubs to re-direct energy to invest in the production of content that can be made available to fans around the world through the clubs&#8217; official social media pages.”</p>
<p>About Stadeum<br />
Digital technology is unlocking unprecedented opportunities in the sports industry, offering the potential to draw fans closer through innovative and customized experiences. To capitalize on this opportunity, however, digital will need to be embedded in every aspect of the business, transforming people, process, and technology. Stadeum Sports helps teams, leagues, and players navigate this digital transformation that is rapidly unlocking new opportunities for growth.</p>
<p>About Audible Magic<br />
For more than 20 years, Audible Magic has innovated solutions to identify content, manage rights, and monetize media. Audible Magic&#8217;s Emmy-winning automatic content recognition (ACR) technology powers billions of transactions monthly. The Silicon Valley pioneer is the trusted intermediary among rightsholders (including labels, studios, distributors, publishers, and collectives) and major platforms.</p>
<p>###</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.audiblemagic.com/2019/07/22/audible-magic-and-stadeum-sports-partner-to-fight-piracy-in-romania/">Audible Magic and Stadeum Sports Partner to Fight Piracy in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.audiblemagic.com">Audible Magic</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
